// Question Types
// 1. MCQs | Multiple Choice | single
// 2. boolean | true/false | single
// 3. MAQs | Multiple Answers | multiple

import { Topic } from ".";

export const amory: Topic = {
  topic: "AMORY WARS",
  level: "Beginner",
  totalQuestions: 150,
  totalScore: 750,
  totalTime: 3600,
  questions: [
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of the governing body that controls the Keywork?",
      choices: [
        "The Red Army",
        "The United Sentry States",
        "The Monstar Rebellion",
        "The Prise Council",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The United Sentry States"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the significance of 'The Crowing' in the Amory Wars narrative?",
      choices: [
        "A mythical creature",
        "A prophecy",
        "A rebellion leader",
        "A starship",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["A prophecy"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which member of Coheed and Cambria has a graphic novel character named after them in the Amory Wars?",
      choices: [
        "Travis Stever",
        "Josh Eppard",
        "Claudio Sanchez",
        "Zach Cooper",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Claudio Sanchez"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of the mysterious energy being that guides the protagonist in 'The Afterman' albums?",
      choices: [
        "The Prize Fighter Inferno",
        "Sirius Amory",
        "The All-Mother",
        "The Ghost of Wilhelm Ryan",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The All-Mother"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 'The Second Stage Turbine Blade,' what is the name of Coheed and Cambria's home planet?",
      choices: ["Heed", "Apity Prime", "Cobalt and Calcium", "Star IV"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Star IV"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which character is known as the 'Ten Speed of God's Blood & Burial' in the Amory Wars narrative?",
      choices: [
        "The Crowing",
        "Al the Killer",
        "The Writer",
        "Mayo Deftinwolf",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Al the Killer"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of the primary antagonist's army in the Amory Wars?",
      choices: [
        "The Red Army",
        "The Prise Legion",
        "The Mayo Rebellion",
        "The Onstantine Priests",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Onstantine Priests"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which Coheed and Cambria album features the character 'Domino the Destitute' in the Amory Wars storyline?",
      choices: [
        "The Unheavenly Creatures",
        "Year of the Black Rainbow",
        "No World for Tomorrow",
        "The Afterman: Descension",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Afterman: Descension"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the name of the spaceship controlled by the Prise?",
      choices: [
        "The Gravemakers & Gunslingers",
        "The Feathers",
        "The Apollo I",
        "The Deconstructed Symphony",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Gravemakers & Gunslingers"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which character is known as the 'Man Your Battlestations' in the Amory Wars narrative?",
      choices: ["Sirius Amory", "Ten Speed", "The All-Mother", "Apollo I"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Apollo I"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of the energy field that protects the Keywork?",
      choices: ["The Fence", "The Shield", "The Veil", "The Barrier"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Veil"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which Coheed and Cambria song is considered the 'unofficial anthem' of the Amory Wars?",
      choices: [
        "Welcome Home",
        "The Suffering",
        "A Favor House Atlantic",
        "The Crowing",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Welcome Home"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of the character who is a key figure in 'The Unheavenly Creatures' narrative?",
      choices: ["Creature", "Vaxis", "Gutter", "Senorita Erminia"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Vaxis"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the significance of the 'Key Entity Extraction'?",
      choices: [
        "A powerful weapon",
        "A method of time travel",
        "A series of prophetic visions",
        "A process of capturing souls",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["A process of capturing souls"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of Coheed and Cambria's home city in 'The Second Stage Turbine Blade'?",
      choices: ["Apity Prime", "Star IV", "Heed", "Newo Ikkin"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Heed"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of the character who wields the 'Keywork Entity' in the Amory Wars?",
      choices: ["The Willing Well", "The Sentry", "The Crowing", "The Inferno"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Crowing"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which Coheed and Cambria album features the character 'Evagria the Faithful'?",
      choices: [
        "The Unheavenly Creatures",
        "Year of the Black Rainbow",
        "The Afterman: Ascension",
        "No World for Tomorrow",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Afterman: Ascension"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of the rebellion group opposing Wilhelm Ryan?",
      choices: [
        "The K.B.I.",
        "The Onstantine Priests",
        "The Monstar Rebellion",
        "The Red Army",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Onstantine Priests"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which member of Coheed and Cambria is known for his concept art contributions to the Amory Wars?",
      choices: [
        "Claudio Sanchez",
        "Travis Stever",
        "Josh Eppard",
        "Zach Cooper",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Travis Stever"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of the character who serves as the primary antagonist in 'Year of the Black Rainbow'?",
      choices: [
        "The All-Mother",
        "Wilhelm Ryan",
        "Mayo Deftinwolf",
        "The Writer",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Wilhelm Ryan"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 'The Second Stage Turbine Blade,' what is the significance of the 'Jersey City Star'?",
      choices: [
        "A weapon of mass destruction",
        "A celestial event",
        "A spaceship",
        "A revolutionary symbol",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["A revolutionary symbol"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which Coheed and Cambria album contains the track 'The Suffering'?",
      choices: [
        "Good Apollo, I'm Burning Star IV: Volume One",
        "In Keeping Secrets of Silent Earth: 3",
        "The Afterman: Descension",
        "The Unheavenly Creatures",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Good Apollo, I'm Burning Star IV: Volume One"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of the entity that guides Claudio Kilgannon's journey in 'The Afterman'?",
      choices: [
        "The All-Mother",
        "The Afterman",
        "The Willing Well",
        "The Key Entity",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The All-Mother"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the function of the 'Monstar Virus'?",
      choices: [
        "Mind control",
        "Time manipulation",
        "Soul extraction",
        "Biological warfare",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Biological warfare"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which Coheed and Cambria album features the character 'The Crowing'?",
      choices: [
        "In Keeping Secrets of Silent Earth: 3",
        "The Second Stage Turbine Blade",
        "Good Apollo, I'm Burning Star IV: Volume One",
        "The Unheavenly Creatures",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["In Keeping Secrets of Silent Earth: 3"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of the character who possesses the 'Key Entity Detections' in 'The Afterman' albums?",
      choices: [
        "The All-Mother",
        "The Sentry",
        "Sirius Amory",
        "The Key Entity",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Sirius Amory"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the fate of the character 'Mayo Deftinwolf'?",
      choices: [
        "Becomes a hero",
        "Suffers amnesia",
        "Dies in battle",
        "Turns into a ghost",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Dies in battle"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of the mysterious force that resurrects characters in 'The Afterman: Descension'?",
      choices: [
        "The Willing Well",
        "The Broken",
        "The Dark Sentencer",
        "The Domino the Destitute",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Domino the Destitute"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which Coheed and Cambria song is inspired by the character 'Ten Speed' in 'The Crowing' narrative?",
      choices: [
        "The Suffering",
        "Welcome Home",
        "The Running Free",
        "Feathers",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Feathers"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 'Good Apollo, I'm Burning Star IV: Volume One,' what is the significance of the 'Burning Star'?",
      choices: [
        "A celestial event",
        "A symbol of rebellion",
        "A spaceship",
        "A mythical creature",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["A celestial event"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of the character who narrates 'The Afterman: Ascension' and 'The Afterman: Descension'?",
      choices: [
        "The Willing Well",
        "Domino the Destitute",
        "Sirius Amory",
        "The All-Mother",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Sirius Amory"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which graphic novel reveals the backstory of Coheed and Cambria's archenemy, Wilhelm Ryan?",
      choices: [
        "Year of the Black Rainbow",
        "In Keeping Secrets of Silent Earth: 3",
        "The Second Stage Turbine Blade",
        "The Unheavenly Creatures",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Year of the Black Rainbow"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of the character who inherits the role of 'The Writer' in 'Good Apollo, I'm Burning Star IV'?",
      choices: [
        "Claudio Kilgannon",
        "Ten Speed",
        "The Crowing",
        "The Prize Fighter Inferno",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Claudio Kilgannon"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the purpose of the 'Monstar Virus' created by Dr. Leonard Hohenberger?",
      choices: [
        "Mind control",
        "Population control",
        "Soul extraction",
        "A tool for peace",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Population control"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of Coheed and Cambria's spaceship in 'The Unheavenly Creatures' narrative?",
      choices: [
        "The Dark Sentencer",
        "The Willing Well",
        "The Vaxis",
        "The Gutter",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Dark Sentencer"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of the character who possesses the 'Key Entity Detections' in 'The Afterman' albums?",
      choices: [
        "The All-Mother",
        "The Sentry",
        "Sirius Amory",
        "The Key Entity",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Sirius Amory"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the fate of the character 'Mayo Deftinwolf'?",
      choices: [
        "Becomes a hero",
        "Suffers amnesia",
        "Dies in battle",
        "Turns into a ghost",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Dies in battle"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of the mysterious force that resurrects characters in 'The Afterman: Descension'?",
      choices: [
        "The Willing Well",
        "The Broken",
        "The Dark Sentencer",
        "The Domino the Destitute",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Domino the Destitute"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which Coheed and Cambria song is inspired by the character 'Ten Speed' in 'The Crowing' narrative?",
      choices: [
        "The Suffering",
        "Welcome Home",
        "The Running Free",
        "Feathers",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Feathers"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 'Good Apollo, I'm Burning Star IV: Volume One,' what is the significance of the 'Burning Star'?",
      choices: [
        "A celestial event",
        "A symbol of rebellion",
        "A spaceship",
        "A mythical creature",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["A celestial event"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of the character who narrates 'The Afterman: Ascension' and 'The Afterman: Descension'?",
      choices: [
        "The Willing Well",
        "Domino the Destitute",
        "Sirius Amory",
        "The All-Mother",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Sirius Amory"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which graphic novel reveals the backstory of Coheed and Cambria's archenemy, Wilhelm Ryan?",
      choices: [
        "Year of the Black Rainbow",
        "In Keeping Secrets of Silent Earth: 3",
        "The Second Stage Turbine Blade",
        "The Unheavenly Creatures",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Year of the Black Rainbow"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of the character who inherits the role of 'The Writer' in 'Good Apollo, I'm Burning Star IV'?",
      choices: [
        "Claudio Kilgannon",
        "Ten Speed",
        "The Crowing",
        "The Prize Fighter Inferno",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Claudio Kilgannon"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the purpose of the 'Monstar Virus' created by Dr. Leonard Hohenberger?",
      choices: [
        "Mind control",
        "Population control",
        "Soul extraction",
        "A tool for peace",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Population control"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of Coheed and Cambria's spaceship in 'The Unheavenly Creatures' narrative?",
      choices: [
        "The Dark Sentencer",
        "The Willing Well",
        "The Vaxis",
        "The Gutter",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Dark Sentencer"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of the character who is the focus of the song 'The Suffering'?",
      choices: [
        "Ten Speed",
        "The All-Mother",
        "The Crowing",
        "The Prize Fighter Inferno",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Crowing"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 'Good Apollo, I'm Burning Star IV: Volume One,' what is the significance of the 'Apollo I'?",
      choices: [
        "A starship",
        "A celestial event",
        "A character's name",
        "A weapon",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["A celestial event"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of the character who goes by the alias 'Al the Killer' in the Amory Wars narrative?",
      choices: [
        "The Crowing",
        "The Prize Fighter Inferno",
        "Claudio Kilgannon",
        "Mayo Deftinwolf",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Mayo Deftinwolf"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which Coheed and Cambria album features the concept of the 'Willing Well'?",
      choices: [
        "In Keeping Secrets of Silent Earth: 3",
        "Good Apollo, I'm Burning Star IV: Volume One",
        "The Unheavenly Creatures",
        "No World for Tomorrow",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Good Apollo, I'm Burning Star IV: Volume One"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the significance of 'The Final Cut'?",
      choices: ["A weapon", "A prophecy", "A spaceship", "A decisive battle"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["A decisive battle"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of the character who is the protagonist in 'The Afterman: Ascension'?",
      choices: [
        "Sirius Amory",
        "The All-Mother",
        "Domino the Destitute",
        "Vaxis",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Sirius Amory"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which Coheed and Cambria album features the character 'Ambellina' in the Amory Wars narrative?",
      choices: [
        "No World for Tomorrow",
        "In Keeping Secrets of Silent Earth: 3",
        "The Unheavenly Creatures",
        "Year of the Black Rainbow",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["In Keeping Secrets of Silent Earth: 3"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 'Year of the Black Rainbow,' what is the role of 'The Onstantine Priests'?",
      choices: [
        "Political leaders",
        "Spiritual guides",
        "Scientific researchers",
        "Warriors",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Scientific researchers"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of the character who is referred to as 'The Prize Fighter Inferno'?",
      choices: [
        "Ten Speed",
        "Claudio Kilgannon",
        "The All-Mother",
        "Sirius Amory",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Claudio Kilgannon"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 'The Second Stage Turbine Blade,' what is the significance of 'The Camper Velorium'?",
      choices: [
        "A weapon",
        "A spaceship",
        "A religious artifact",
        "A secret organization",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["A spaceship"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of the character who represents the 'Key Entity Extraction' in 'Good Apollo, I'm Burning Star IV'?",
      choices: [
        "The Writer",
        "Domino the Destitute",
        "The Crowing",
        "The All-Mother",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Writer"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the role of the character 'Newo Ikkin'?",
      choices: [
        "A prophet",
        "A scientist",
        "A political leader",
        "A love interest",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["A love interest"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which Coheed and Cambria album features the character 'Mother Superior'?",
      choices: [
        "The Afterman: Descension",
        "In Keeping Secrets of Silent Earth: 3",
        "No World for Tomorrow",
        "The Unheavenly Creatures",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["No World for Tomorrow"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of the character who is the main antagonist in 'In Keeping Secrets of Silent Earth: 3'?",
      choices: ["Wilhelm Ryan", "Mayo Deftinwolf", "The Writer", "Ambellina"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Wilhelm Ryan"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the purpose of the 'Pryor Glass'?",
      choices: [
        "A powerful artifact",
        "A communication device",
        "A spaceship",
        "A source of energy",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["A communication device"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of Coheed and Cambria's daughter in the Amory Wars narrative?",
      choices: [
        "Pearl of Heart",
        "Chase the Morning",
        "Erica Court",
        "A Favor House Atlantic",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Erica Court"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which character is known as 'The Dark Sentencer' in the Amory Wars narrative?",
      choices: [
        "The Prize Fighter Inferno",
        "Sirius Amory",
        "Vaxis",
        "Wilhelm Ryan",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Dark Sentencer"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of the celestial object that is a recurring theme in Coheed and Cambria's music?",
      choices: ["The Moon", "The Star", "The Comet", "The Sun"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Keywork"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 'Year of the Black Rainbow,' what is the occupation of Dr. Leonard Hohenberger?",
      choices: ["Scientist", "Soldier", "Politician", "Engineer"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Scientist"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which Coheed and Cambria album is a prequel to the Amory Wars narrative?",
      choices: [
        "Year of the Black Rainbow",
        "The Afterman: Ascension",
        "No World for Tomorrow",
        "In Keeping Secrets of Silent Earth: 3",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Year of the Black Rainbow"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of Coheed and Cambria's spaceship in 'The Afterman: Ascension'?",
      choices: [
        "The Domino the Destitute",
        "The Willing Well",
        "The Dark Sentencer",
        "The Key Entity",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Domino the Destitute"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 'The Second Stage Turbine Blade,' what is the significance of the 'Jesse, Bad Boy'?",
      choices: [
        "A character's name",
        "A mythical creature",
        "A starship",
        "A revolutionary symbol",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["A revolutionary symbol"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which character is known as the 'Holly Wood the Cracked' in the Amory Wars narrative?",
      choices: ["Ten Speed", "The All-Mother", "Ambellina", "Mayo Deftinwolf"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Ten Speed"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of the character who is a central figure in 'The Afterman: Descension'?",
      choices: [
        "The Prize Fighter Inferno",
        "The Domino the Destitute",
        "Vaxis",
        "Sirius Amory",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Vaxis"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the purpose of the 'Key Entity Extraction'?",
      choices: [
        "A powerful weapon",
        "A method of time travel",
        "A series of prophetic visions",
        "A process of capturing souls",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["A process of capturing souls"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of the character who is a member of 'The Prise' in the Amory Wars?",
      choices: [
        "The All-Mother",
        "The Onstantine Priests",
        "Sirius Amory",
        "Domino the Destitute",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The All-Mother"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which Coheed and Cambria song is considered the 'epic conclusion' of the Amory Wars narrative?",
      choices: [
        "The Crowing",
        "The End Complete",
        "The Willing Well IV: The Final Cut",
        "Welcome Home",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Willing Well IV: The Final Cut"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of the character who is known as the 'Willing Well' in the Amory Wars?",
      choices: [
        "The Writer",
        "Claudio Kilgannon",
        "Domino the Destitute",
        "Ambellina",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Claudio Kilgannon"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 'Year of the Black Rainbow,' what is the role of the character 'Mariah Antillarea'?",
      choices: ["Scientist", "Spy", "Rebel leader", "Love interest"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Scientist"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which Coheed and Cambria album features the character 'The Hollow'?",
      choices: [
        "The Afterman: Descension",
        "No World for Tomorrow",
        "Good Apollo, I'm Burning Star IV: Volume One",
        "In Keeping Secrets of Silent Earth: 3",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["In Keeping Secrets of Silent Earth: 3"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of the protagonist couple in 'The Second Stage Turbine Blade'?",
      choices: [
        "Claudio and Cambria",
        "Jesse and Holly",
        "Coheed and Cambria",
        "Ambellina and Ten Speed",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Coheed and Cambria"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 'The Second Stage Turbine Blade,' what is the name of Coheed and Cambria's home city?",
      choices: ["Heed", "Apity Prime", "Star IV", "Newo Ikkin"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Heed"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the significance of 'The Camper Velorium' in 'The Second Stage Turbine Blade'?",
      choices: [
        "A weapon",
        "A spaceship",
        "A religious artifact",
        "A secret organization",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["A spaceship"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Who serves as the primary antagonist in 'The Second Stage Turbine Blade'?",
      choices: ["Wilhelm Ryan", "Mayo Deftinwolf", "The Writer", "Ten Speed"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Wilhelm Ryan"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of the rebellion group opposing Wilhelm Ryan in 'The Second Stage Turbine Blade'?",
      choices: [
        "The Onstantine Priests",
        "The K.B.I.",
        "The Red Army",
        "The Monstar Rebellion",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Onstantine Priests"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the occupation of the character 'Jesse, Bad Boy'?",
      choices: ["Mechanic", "Artist", "Scientist", "Musician"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Mechanic"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of Coheed and Cambria's spaceship in 'The Second Stage Turbine Blade'?",
      choices: [
        "The Dark Sentencer",
        "The Willing Well",
        "The Keywork",
        "The Velorium Camper",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Velorium Camper"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Who plays a significant role as a guiding entity in 'The Second Stage Turbine Blade'?",
      choices: [
        "Domino the Destitute",
        "The All-Mother",
        "The Key Entity",
        "Ambellina",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Ambellina"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What event leads to the rebellion against Wilhelm Ryan in 'The Second Stage Turbine Blade'?",
      choices: [
        "The Camper Velorium's arrival",
        "The birth of a child",
        "The discovery of a secret weapon",
        "The destruction of Heed",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The birth of a child"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the role of 'The Key Entity' in 'The Second Stage Turbine Blade' narrative?",
      choices: [
        "A weapon",
        "A guiding force",
        "A source of power",
        "A prophetic figure",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["A guiding force"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of Coheed and Cambria's home city in 'The Second Stage Turbine Blade'?",
      choices: ["Heed", "Star IV", "Apity Prime", "Heaven's Fence"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Heed"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Who serves as the primary antagonist in 'The Second Stage Turbine Blade'?",
      choices: ["Wilhelm Ryan", "Mayo Deftinwolf", "Ten Speed", "Ambellina"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Wilhelm Ryan"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the occupation of the character 'Jesse, Bad Boy' in the comics?",
      choices: ["Mechanic", "Artist", "Scientist", "Musician"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Mechanic"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What event leads to the rebellion against Wilhelm Ryan in 'The Second Stage Turbine Blade'?",
      choices: [
        "The Camper Velorium's arrival",
        "The birth of a child",
        "The destruction of Heed",
        "The discovery of a secret weapon",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The birth of a child"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of Coheed and Cambria's spaceship in the comics?",
      choices: [
        "The Velorium Camper",
        "The Dark Sentencer",
        "The Willing Well",
        "The Keywork",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Velorium Camper"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Who plays a significant role as a guiding entity in 'The Second Stage Turbine Blade'?",
      choices: [
        "Ambellina",
        "Domino the Destitute",
        "The All-Mother",
        "The Key Entity",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Ambellina"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the significance of 'The Camper Velorium' in the comics?",
      choices: [
        "A spaceship",
        "A religious artifact",
        "A revolutionary symbol",
        "A mythical creature",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["A spaceship"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 'The Second Stage Turbine Blade,' what is the role of 'The Key Entity'?",
      choices: [
        "A weapon",
        "A guiding force",
        "A source of power",
        "A prophetic figure",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["A guiding force"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of the protagonist couple in 'The Second Stage Turbine Blade'?",
      choices: [
        "Jesse and Holly",
        "Ambellina and Claudio",
        "Ten Speed and Erica Court",
        "Coheed and Cambria",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Coheed and Cambria"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the role of 'Heaven's Fence'?",
      choices: [
        "A celestial event",
        "A protective barrier",
        "A spaceship",
        "A mythical creature",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["A protective barrier"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 'In Keeping Secrets of Silent Earth: 3,' what is the name of the city where the story primarily unfolds?",
      choices: ["Heed", "Star IV", "Apity Prime", "Silent Earth"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Heed"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Who is the primary antagonist in 'In Keeping Secrets of Silent Earth: 3'?",
      choices: ["Wilhelm Ryan", "Mayo Deftinwolf", "Ten Speed", "Ambellina"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Wilhelm Ryan"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the significance of 'The Keywork' in the comics?",
      choices: [
        "A weapon",
        "A celestial event",
        "A spaceship",
        "A source of power",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["A source of power"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In the comics, who is the central character on a quest to prevent the destruction of Heaven's Fence?",
      choices: [
        "Ambellina",
        "Domino the Destitute",
        "Claudio Kilgannon",
        "Sirius Amory",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Claudio Kilgannon"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of the mysterious organization that plays a significant role in 'In Keeping Secrets of Silent Earth: 3'?",
      choices: [
        "The Monstar Rebellion",
        "The Onstantine Priests",
        "The K.B.I.",
        "The Gravemakers & Gunslingers",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Onstantine Priests"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the role of the character 'Domino the Destitute' in the storyline?",
      choices: [
        "A guiding force",
        "A revolutionary leader",
        "A mythical creature",
        "A prisoner",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["A prisoner"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What event leads to the rebellion against Wilhelm Ryan in 'In Keeping Secrets of Silent Earth: 3'?",
      choices: [
        "The birth of a child",
        "The destruction of Heed",
        "The discovery of a secret weapon",
        "The release of a deadly virus",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The release of a deadly virus"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the role of the character 'Ambellina'?",
      choices: [
        "A love interest",
        "A guiding force",
        "A revolutionary leader",
        "A mythical creature",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["A guiding force"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of the character who represents the 'Key Entity Extraction' in 'In Keeping Secrets of Silent Earth: 3'?",
      choices: [
        "The Writer",
        "The Crowing",
        "The All-Mother",
        "Claudio Kilgannon",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Crowing"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the purpose of the 'Holly Wood the Cracked' in the comics?",
      choices: [
        "A weapon",
        "A spaceship",
        "A prophetic figure",
        "A source of power",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["A prophetic figure"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of the protagonist in 'In Keeping Secrets of Silent Earth: 3' comics?",
      choices: ["Claudio Kilgannon", "Ambellina", "Ten Speed", "Sirius Amory"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Claudio Kilgannon"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the primary goal of Claudio Kilgannon?",
      choices: [
        "Seek revenge",
        "Prevent the destruction of Heaven's Fence",
        "Master the Keywork",
        "Overthrow Wilhelm Ryan",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Prevent the destruction of Heaven's Fence"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the significance of the character 'Ambellina' in 'In Keeping Secrets of Silent Earth: 3'?",
      choices: [
        "A love interest",
        "A guiding force",
        "A revolutionary leader",
        "A mythical creature",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["A guiding force"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the role of 'The Onstantine Priests'?",
      choices: [
        "Protectors of the Keywork",
        "Cult leaders",
        "Heaven's Fence administrators",
        "Assassins working for Wilhelm Ryan",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Assassins working for Wilhelm Ryan"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of the city where most of the action takes place in 'In Keeping Secrets of Silent Earth: 3'?",
      choices: ["Heed", "Star IV", "Silent Earth", "Apity Prime"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Heed"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Who plays a crucial role as a prophetic figure in 'In Keeping Secrets of Silent Earth: 3'?",
      choices: [
        "Domino the Destitute",
        "The Writer",
        "The All-Mother",
        "The Crowing",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Crowing"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the role of the character 'Holly Wood the Cracked'?",
      choices: [
        "A weapon",
        "A spaceship",
        "A prophetic figure",
        "A source of power",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["A prophetic figure"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What event leads to the rebellion against Wilhelm Ryan in 'In Keeping Secrets of Silent Earth: 3'?",
      choices: [
        "The birth of a child",
        "The destruction of Heed",
        "The release of a deadly virus",
        "The discovery of a secret weapon",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The release of a deadly virus"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the significance of the character 'Al the Killer' in the comics?",
      choices: [
        "A legendary warrior",
        "A serial killer",
        "A revolutionary leader",
        "A hidden ally of Claudio",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["A serial killer"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of Claudio's weapon in 'In Keeping Secrets of Silent Earth: 3'?",
      choices: [
        "The Monstar",
        "The Keywork Blade",
        "The Morningstar",
        "The Crowing's Wrath",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Morningstar"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Who is the guardian of the 'Keywork' in 'In Keeping Secrets of Silent Earth: 3'?",
      choices: ["The Writer", "The All-Mother", "The Crowing", "Ambellina"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The All-Mother"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the purpose of the 'Pryor Glass'?",
      choices: [
        "A powerful artifact",
        "A communication device",
        "A spaceship",
        "A source of energy",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["A communication device"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of the celestial object that is a recurring theme in 'In Keeping Secrets of Silent Earth: 3'?",
      choices: ["The Moon", "The Star", "The Comet", "The Keywork"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Keywork"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which character is known as 'The Running Free' in the 'In Keeping Secrets of Silent Earth: 3' narrative?",
      choices: ["The Crowing", "Claudio Kilgannon", "Ambellina", "Ten Speed"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Ambellina"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of the character who possesses the 'Key Entity Detections' in the comics?",
      choices: ["Vaxis", "The Crowing", "The All-Mother", "Sirius Amory"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Vaxis"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the role of the character 'Mariah Antillarea' in 'In Keeping Secrets of Silent Earth: 3'?",
      choices: ["Scientist", "Spy", "Rebel leader", "Love interest"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Scientist"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which Coheed and Cambria album serves as a prequel to the events in 'In Keeping Secrets of Silent Earth: 3'?",
      choices: [
        "The Afterman: Descension",
        "Year of the Black Rainbow",
        "No World for Tomorrow",
        "The Second Stage Turbine Blade",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Year of the Black Rainbow"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the occupation of the character 'Dr. Leonard Hohenberger'?",
      choices: ["Scientist", "Soldier", "Politician", "Engineer"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Scientist"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of the character who is a prominent figure in 'The Unheavenly Creatures' storyline?",
      choices: ["Gutter", "Creature", "Senorita Erminia", "Vaxis"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Creature"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the ultimate goal of Claudio Kilgannon in 'In Keeping Secrets of Silent Earth: 3'?",
      choices: [
        "Conquer the Keywork",
        "Defeat Wilhelm Ryan",
        "Find his lost love",
        "Unlock the secrets of the Monstar",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Defeat Wilhelm Ryan"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Who is the primary antagonist in 'Good Apollo, I’m Burning Star IV: Vol. 1 – From Fear Through The Eyes of Madness'?",
      choices: ["Wilhelm Ryan", "Mayo Deftinwolf", "The Writer", "Ambellina"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Writer"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the significance of 'The Amory Wars'?",
      choices: [
        "A war between planets",
        "A series of prophetic visions",
        "A rebellion against an oppressive ruler",
        "A cosmic conflict fueled by music",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["A cosmic conflict fueled by music"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of the character who assumes the identity of 'The Crowing' in the storyline?",
      choices: [
        "Claudio Kilgannon",
        "Domino the Destitute",
        "Ambellina",
        "Ten Speed",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Claudio Kilgannon"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Who serves as a guiding force to Claudio Kilgannon in 'Good Apollo, I’m Burning Star IV: Vol. 1 – From Fear Through The Eyes of Madness'?",
      choices: [
        "The All-Mother",
        "The Key Entity",
        "The Writer",
        "The Onstantine Priests",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Writer"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the role of the character 'Al the Killer'?",
      choices: [
        "A companion to Claudio",
        "A serial killer",
        "A rebel leader",
        "A guardian of the Keywork",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["A serial killer"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What event triggers Claudio Kilgannon's quest for revenge in 'Good Apollo, I’m Burning Star IV: Vol. 1'?",
      choices: [
        "The destruction of his home planet",
        "The betrayal of a friend",
        "The death of a loved one",
        "A vision from The Keywork",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The death of a loved one"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of Coheed and Cambria's spaceship in the comics?",
      choices: [
        "The Velorium Camper",
        "The Dark Sentencer",
        "The Willing Well",
        "The Keywork",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Velorium Camper"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which celestial object is a key element in the 'Good Apollo, I’m Burning Star IV: Vol. 1' narrative?",
      choices: ["The Moon", "The Star", "The Comet", "The Keywork"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Keywork"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the significance of 'The Gravemakers & Gunslingers' in the comics?",
      choices: [
        "A rebel group",
        "A mythical creature",
        "An army of Wilhelm Ryan",
        "A spaceship",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["A rebel group"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 'Good Apollo, I’m Burning Star IV: Vol. 1,' what is the role of 'The Prize Fighter Inferno'?",
      choices: [
        "A secret organization",
        "A weapon of mass destruction",
        "A guardian of the Keywork",
        "A persona assumed by Claudio Kilgannon",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["A persona assumed by Claudio Kilgannon"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Who assumes the role of 'The Prise' in 'Good Apollo, I’m Burning Star IV: Vol. 1'?",
      choices: ["Ambellina", "Ten Speed", "Erica Court", "The All-Mother"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Ambellina"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the purpose of 'The Key Entity Extraction'?",
      choices: [
        "A weapon",
        "A method of time travel",
        "A series of prophetic visions",
        "A process of capturing souls",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["A process of capturing souls"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of the character who represents the 'Key Entity Extraction' in 'Good Apollo, I’m Burning Star IV: Vol. 1'?",
      choices: [
        "The Writer",
        "The Crowing",
        "Claudio Kilgannon",
        "The Prize Fighter Inferno",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Crowing"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What event leads to the revelation of Claudio Kilgannon as 'The Crowing'?",
      choices: [
        "The destruction of a city",
        "The death of Ambellina",
        "A confrontation with The Writer",
        "A journey through the Keywork",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["A confrontation with The Writer"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the role of the character 'Chase Ambulance'?",
      choices: [
        "A member of The Prise",
        "A rebel leader",
        "A guide for Claudio",
        "An assassin working for Wilhelm Ryan",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["A guide for Claudio"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of the organization that opposes The Writer in 'Good Apollo, I’m Burning Star IV: Vol. 1'?",
      choices: [
        "The Gravemakers & Gunslingers",
        "The Onstantine Priests",
        "The Red Army",
        "The K.B.I.",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Gravemakers & Gunslingers"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the significance of 'The Hollow'?",
      choices: [
        "A mythical creature",
        "A weapon of mass destruction",
        "A spaceship",
        "A city in the Keywork",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["A city in the Keywork"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of the character who is a crucial figure in 'Good Apollo, I’m Burning Star IV: Vol. 1' and represents the 'White Ruineer'?",
      choices: [
        "Mariah Antillarea",
        "The Prize Fighter Inferno",
        "Ten Speed",
        "Erica Court",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Mariah Antillarea"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the significance of 'The Dark Sentencer'?",
      choices: [
        "A weapon",
        "A spaceship",
        "A prophecy",
        "A method of time travel",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["A spaceship"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the role of the character 'The Burning Star IV' in the storyline?",
      choices: [
        "A celestial event",
        "A weapon of mass destruction",
        "A spaceship",
        "A source of power",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["A celestial event"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 'The Amory Wars' narrative, what is the name of the sentient energy force that maintains the Keywork?",
      choices: [
        "The Writer",
        "The Crowing",
        "The Keywork",
        "The Prize Fighter Inferno",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Keywork"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "The character 'The Crowing' plays a significant role in 'The Amory Wars.' What is the real name of 'The Crowing'?",
      choices: [
        "Sirius Amory",
        "Claudio Kilgannon",
        "Ambellina",
        "Coheed Kilgannon",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Claudio Kilgannon"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the central theme of 'The Amory Wars' storyline, focusing on the conflict between the Red Army and the rebellion?",
      choices: [
        "The Great Crash",
        "The Second Stage Turbine Blade",
        "The Year of the Black Rainbow",
        "The Keywork Chronicles",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Second Stage Turbine Blade"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 'The Amory Wars,' what is the name of the primary antagonist who seeks to control the Keywork for ultimate power?",
      choices: [
        "Maynard James Keenan",
        "General Mayo Deftinwolf",
        "The Dark Sentencer",
        "Vic the Butcher",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["General Mayo Deftinwolf"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which graphic novel serves as a prequel to 'The Amory Wars' and delves into the origins of Coheed and Cambria Kilgannon?",
      choices: [
        "The Afterman",
        "The Bag.On.Line Adventures",
        "The Keywork Chronicles",
        "The Second Stage Turbine Blade",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Second Stage Turbine Blade"],
      score: 5,
    },
  ],
};
